Rebecca Lacer

720-217-7983

r.a.lacer@hotmail.com

LinkedIn

Digital Portfolio

The skills I've learned as a University of Denver coding student, pair well with my experience working in Quality Assurance. As a team member for a large manufacturing facility. My basic data review skills were used to release finished product, accept or reject raw materials, and many other things. An example of deep dive data review, would be to identify the scope of a cross functional team project, generally to address something like under performing divisional quality metrics, such as consumer complaints.

Technical Skills:

As a current student, I have developed web applications using HTML, CSS, Javascript and am currently learning Node.js. Some of my projects include a day planner and a password generator, as well as a music application to sample songs from a particular artist. Check them out here: https://github.com/RLacer

Employment and Experience:

08//2020-09/2020 (temporary)

Bureau of Census

Denver, CO

NRFU Enumerator

Completing census questionnaires for non-respondents. This was an interesting position; you never know what you'll get knocking on someone's front door as a representative of the US Government.

01/2018 - 06/2019

Nestle Purina PetCare Company

Denver, CO

Quality Operations Team Leader

Data Review: Raw Materials, In Process, Finished Product, Consumer Complaints

Data Analysis for project parameters in support of Continuous Improvement

<u>Sampling Plans</u>: Routine Sampling on Raw Materials, In Process and Finished Product, Hold Product Sampling and Final Disposition

<u>Audits and Document Control</u>: Complete Document Control, Policy and Procedural Compliance, Audit Prep-internal, external, regulatory – both planned and unplanned visits

Regulatory experience dealing with the FDA and ISO 22000 & FSSC 22000, both as a team member and a lead for planned and unplanned visits

Trace and Recall for holds. Quarterly mock trace as part of a cross functional team, as required by policy (experience as lead and team member)

Certification: Preventive Controls Qualified Individual as defined in 21 CFR Part 507

<u>Current Good Manufacturing Practice, Hazard Analysis, and Risk-Based Preventive Controls for</u>
<u>Food For Animals</u> (Revised as of April 1, 2017)

<u>Misc</u>: Expense Reporting, payroll review, employee performance evaluations, inventory, chemical control

The above is an overview of some of my responsibilities.

One of the last procedural implementations I led, occurred in the finished product and ingredient labs.

There was a newly approved rapid alternative method for testing ingredients and finished product. The new method had the same range of accuracy as standard method. I solicited feedback from all affected individuals and my team was very excited for the change. With

corporate support, Denver was the first facility in the division to cutover. The results were amazing. There was overtime reduction and increased team morale. There were additional cost savings due to reduced chemical inventory and laboratory consumables. Internal control points and data recording were streamlined. Hold product had a quicker turnaround and lengthy lab chemical control policies were greatly reduced because many of the chemicals became obsolete.

03/2006 - 01/2018

Nestle Purina PetCare Company

Denver, CO

Analyst II

I began with Nestle Purina as the 2nd shift finished product lab analyst. I also worked as the ingredient specialist and even when my roles changed, I continued to backup the finished product lab, ingredient lab and packing room. Additional roles included Quality Management Functional Expert for SAP and QA SME for MES Systems. I enjoy receiving and delivering coaching and training. I believe there is always more to learn and more to know.

02/2002-02/2006

Evergreen Analytical Lab

Wheatridge, CO

Lab Tech/Analyst

This was an NELAC Certified environmental lab. As an entry level tech, I did metals prep. This included strong acid digests on soil and water samples, in preparation to be analyzed by mass spectrometer. I later moved to wet chem. This department did more "bench testing". Many of the samples came from municipal water treatment facilities and we were the 3rd party lab used to confirm EPA compliance.

01/2001-01/2002

ATA Airlines

Denver, CO

Airport Customer Service Agent

There was a time when air travel required checking in with a person, that was me. I also worked to recover lost luggage and process damage claims. After nine eleven I was an instant security guard.

Education:

University of Denver

Full Stack Web Development (02/2021-present)

Front Range Community College, Westminster Colorado

Associate of Science, Math Emphasis (1997)

Emily Griffith Opportunity School, Denver, CO

Airframe & Power Plant Mechanics Certificate (1991)

Basic Electricity & Electronics (1991)